realitydesu.com 2012-06-10

# Privacy Policy - Reality Desu Community Forums - A Games and Anime Resource Center

### Forum Privacy Policy for http://forums.realitydesu.com  
and  
  
Last Updated: 5th September 2009 

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at cubedadmin@chencubed.com.

The privacy of our visitors to http://forums.realitydesu.com is important to us.

At Reality Desu Community Forums - A Games and Anime Resource Center, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit http://forums.realitydesu.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. 

## Google Adsense 3rd Party Cookie Info

  * Log Files
  * Cookies and Beacons
  * DoubleClick DART cookies

As with most other websites, http://forums.realitydesu.com collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

http://forums.realitydesu.com do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. We also use third party advertisements on http://forums.realitydesu.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google's ™ DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests "(interest based targeting"). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

http://forums.realitydesu.com has complied with the following Webmaster guidelines:  
**[Technical guidelines  
](http://www.google.com/support/webmasters/bin/answer.py?answer=35769#2)[Quality guidelines](http://www.google.com/support/webmasters/bin/answer.py?answer=35769#3)

## Forum Privacy Policy 

  * Registration
  * Inappropriate Language
  * Posting Links
  * Security
  * Ad Servers
  * Opt-Out Policy
  * Consent
  * Disclaimer

Registration is not necessary for the public to use this Web site. However, members must register in order to gain access to adding threads to the Web site. During registration, you must complete the registration form and create a user name and password. During registration you are required to give us contact information. We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest.

http://forums.realitydesu.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this Web site.

The use of inappropriate or offensive language is not permitted in these forums. Inappropriate or offensive language includes, but is not limited to, any language or content that is sexually oriented, sexually suggestive or abusive, harassing, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, profane, hateful, or that contains racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable material of any kind. We ask that you please be considerate to other members in the forums when posting your messages.

Our policy on linking to other forums is pretty simple. Members may link to any other site that provides information that helps answer another member's question or is just of general interest to members of that particular forum. One of the most basic tenets of the Web is the open exchange of information. 

http://forums.realitydesu.com follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:  

**If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at:**  
cubedadmin@chencubed.com

We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:  
Opting not to register to receive our electronic newsletters.  
Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our users

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by http://forums.realitydesu.com. 

http://forums.realitydesu.com reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

**DoubleClick Opt-out Click link below**

AdSense Privacy Policy Provided by [**Tutorials4you**](http://www.tutorials4you.co.uk/index.php)
